SADD.IO Privacy Policy

This policy effective 12/05/2019

Jackson CS Consulting, LLC ("us", "we", or "our") operates https://sadd.io (the

"Site"). This page informs you of our policies regarding your information.

Summary

Nothing in this policy contradicts the following statements:

1. The user is not obligated to provide real information to communicate with us or operate

our services.

2. We do not collect any of your personal information.

3. We do not sell your information to third parties.

4. We do not log any user access or activity.

Users are not obligated to provide real information to communicate with us

or operate the site

You may use third party tools to hide your personal information. This includes but is not limited

to VPNs, disposable emails, spoofed numbers, and cryptocurrency.

We do not collect any of your personal information

We use Selly and its payment gateways (PayPal, Stripe, and Cryptocurrency) to process

payments. All processed payments return a order ID (“access token”). We give you access to a

generated desktop, if the access token that you provide is connected with a payment that was

successfully processed within the last 30 days. We also use Zendesk to conduct live chat with

you. Finally, we use Cloudflare to protect our website and servers. It is important to check the

privacy policies of these third parties as they may differ from our privacy policy.

We do not sell your information to third parties

Since we do not collect any of your personal information, we do not sell any of your personal

information to third parties.

We do not log any user access or activity

Your activity is not logged by any of our systems. Any activity occurring on the desktops that

you generate, is forensically destroyed at the end of the time limit in which you specify. There is

no way to recover this data.

Changes to this policy

We may make changes to this policy without notice to you, so you are encouraged to review the

policy from time to time.

Contact

You can contact us at support@sadd.io if you have any questions about this policy.
